Scott Plomer

401 Anderson Street, College Station TX 77845 ■ (813)-7279024 ■ SCPlomer27@gmail.com

Profile

Over a year experience in front-end web development languages. Wrote and deployed several apps and web pages. Years of experience in leadership roles in high stress environments. Worked directly with clients on problem solving their service needs and organizing maintenance on large scale sites. Comfortable in construction, group, unsupervised, and high precision environments.

Group Management

Public Speaking

Summary of Skills

Quick Learner Writina Positive Attitude Microsoft Word/Excel/Access

Work Experience		
	Fire Protection - Fire Alarm Service Manager/Sales Ran the fire alarm and extinguisher service team. Developed financial reporting systems.	February 2019 - Present
0	Worked directly with customers to sell and perform service on their systems.	
	Created an education system for service technicians a exams.	and office personnel for certification
	can Fire Protection Group - FAL Service Tech Trained new employees increasing service quality.	September 2017 - February 2019
	Managed and led on site inspections and service crev Obtained multiple licenses and developed educationa employees.	
	Programmed fire alarm panels.	
_	t - Audio Visual Installer Led groups on site in an multi-million dollar construction	February 2017 - September 2017 on project for Texas A&M.
PSAV	- PT Audio Visual Technician	June 2016 - September 2017

Education

Texas A&M University College Station, TX, USA

2012 - 2016

Bachelor of Arts: Telecommunication Media Studies GPA of 3.88

My minors are in Business Administration and Philosophy. High School Diploma from Katy HS.

Interests

Hiking, Video Production and Editing, Competitive Powerlifting, Live Streaming, MMA